Cock-a-doodle-who????
Hatching Pete is a family, comedy, tv movie film directed by Stuart Gillard.
Pete is very inconspicuous at school, unlike his extrovert mate Cleatis who's happy to don a chicken
suit and be the school mascot, but unfortunately, Cleatis is allergic to the suit.
When there's an uproar at the chicken's disappearance, Pete is forced into the
limelight as the school's basketball reputation is at stake.
Pete Ivey, played by Jason Dolley.
Cleatis Poole, played by Mitchel Musso.
Jamie Wynn, played by Tiffany Thornton.
Angela Morrissey, played by Josie Loren.
Wendell Pate, played by Aramis Knight.
Leon Ivey, played by Sean O'Bryan.
Hatching Pete is a 2009 American comedy film released
as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
It first aired on April 24, 2009, on Disney Channel UK
and later Disney Channel and Family.
It was released on DVD in America on May 12, 2009, together with Dadnapped.
The tone is lighthearted.